<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Corrective exercises</string>
    <string name="bmi_explain">Body mass index (BMI) is a statistical measure used to compare a person\'s weight and height.\n In fact.\n this test does not measure the rate of obesity.\n but is a suitable tool to estimate the health of a person\'s weight according to his height.\n This index was invented between 1830 and 1850 by the Belgian scientist Adolf Kotle</string>
    <string name="bmr_explain">The basal metabolic rate. or bmr.\n is the total amount of calories your body needs that performs the normal. basic function of the blood at rest. These basic functions include blood circulation. respiration. cell division. protein synthesis. ion transport. energy utilization by muscles. nerves. and cells.</string>
    <string name="laghar">Your weight is a little low.\n Here are some tips to gain weight. \nExercise is one of the most important factors not only for losing weight but also for gaining weight. So do not forget to exercise.\n Eat high-protein foods such as dairy, meat, soy, and high-carbohydrate foods such as pasta, rice, and whole grains. Drink eight to ten glasses of water a day.\n High-fat foods and fast foods are very harmful to the body, so do not use them.\n Lack of sleep also causes weight loss and too much sleep is harmful to the body.\n Adjust your sleep duration to about 8 hours a day.</string>
    <string name="tabiei">Your weight is normal.\n Here are some tips to maintain a normal weight.\n Exercise regularly.\n You do not need to go to the gym to exercise, but with simple exercises at home you can ensure your health.\n Avoid sleeping too much or sleeping too late.\n The best time to sleep is about eight hours a day.\n Avoid fast foods. Your body needs eight to ten glasses of water daily.</string>
    <string name="ezafevazn">You are a little overweight but do not worry because you can easily reach a normal weight by following the tips below.\n Exercise is always one of the most important factors in health.\n Exercise can cause both weight loss and weight gain, and it depends on the type of exercise you do.\n Another thing you can do to lose weight is to change your diet.\n You should eat light foods such as salads and fruits and avoid heavy foods such as kebabs.\n One of the most important causes of obesity and overweight is eating fast food, so in order to achieve a normal weight, you should avoid eating fast food.</string>
    <string name="chagh">You are obese.\n As you know, obesity can cause many diseases, so you should plan to lose weight to maintain your health.\n Here are some tips to lose weight. The most important Obesity is caused by overeating, so eat less and avoid heavy meals as much as you can.\n Exercise is something that everyone recommends for obese and thin people.\n Try to run daily. It may be difficult at first, but it is not a problem. In the first days, run a short route and you do not need to run a long distance, but try to increase the route every day to achieve the desired result.\nSleep less! Too much sleep will cause obesity, so it is better not to spend more than eight hours a day sleeping.</string>
    <string name="about">Sports Sciences of Damghan University   Prepared by Dr. Maliheh Ardakanizadeh.\n PhD in Sports Physiology and Faculty Member of Damghan University.\n and Mr. Hossein Yuzbashinejad and Mr. Mohammad Reza Mousavi.\n undergraduate students in the field of sports sciences.\n\n  Developer:\nMr. Mohammad Hossein Gilanpanah\n\n Grapist: Ms. Zahra Afshari\n\n  Contact with BideMajnoon:\n  korosh5775@gmail.com </string>
    <string name="skip">skip</string>
    <string name="next">next</string>
    <string name="done">start</string>
    <string name="poshte_gerd">kyphosis</string>
    <string name="gardane_kaj">torticollis</string>
    <string name="paye_god">supinated foot</string>
    <string name="paye_saf">flat foot</string>
    <string name="lagan">asymmetric pelvis</string>
    <string name="paye_x">genu valgum</string>
    <string name="paye_parantezi">genu varum</string>
    <string name="poshte_god">lordosis</string>
    <string name="poshte_kaj">Scoliosis</string>
    <string name="sarbejelo">forward head</string>
    <string name="shane">uneven shoulders</string>
    <string name="shast">hallux valgus</string>
    <string name="changali">claw toe</string>
    <string name="chakoshi">hammer toe</string>

    <string name="areze_poshte_gerd">The dorsal arch of the spine is normally called kyphosis.\n which will turn into a complication called hyperkyphosis and requires medical attention if it is more than normal.\n This abnormality is a condition in which the arch of the thoracic spine becomes abnormal and tends to bend forward.\n causing respiratory problems in the affected people.\n In this abnormality.\n the anterior and thoracic muscles.\n such as the pectoralis major and small.\n and the arm\'s inner rotators.\n are shortened.\n and the muscles that straighten the spine and the anterior dentition become weak.\n Classification of kyphosis: Postural kyphosis: This type of kyphosis is caused by adopting an inappropriate physical position.\n The most common type of kyphosis is postural kyphosis.\n which occurs naturally in young people and the elderly.\n This abnormality can be corrected by correcting the resulting muscle imbalance.\n With age.\n the stability of the musculoskeletal system decreases.\n and kyphosis increases.\n Structural kyphosis: This abnormality is caused by factors such as abnormalities in the bones.\n intervertebral discs.\n nerves.\n ligaments.\n or muscles.\n In people with structural kyphosis.\n medical interventions should be used because the progression of the disease cannot be prevented without medical intervention</string>
    <string name="elat_poshte_gerd">1- Increasing thoracic or dorsal arch.\n 2- Falling shoulders forward and approaching the chin to the chest.\n 3- Shrinking the chest and related muscles.\n 4- Creating a bulge on the abdominal wall and hanging it down.\n 5- Protruding the scapula.\n 6- Flattening of the arch or lordosis of the back and neck.\n</string>
    <string name="test_poshte_gerd">One of the simplest and most common tests for this type of complication is the use of a vertical line.\n which is a normal people from the bottom to the top.\n passes from the outer part of the ankle.\n the side and the outer part of the patella of the knee.\n the center of the lateral and outer part of the pelvis.\n the center of the shoulder bone and the eardrum.\n In a people with around the back of the earlobe and the center of the shoulder.\n bone is in front of the line.\n and the center of the lateral and outer part of the pelvis is behind the vertical line of the people.\n</string>

    <string name="areze_gardane_kaj">The torticollis is a kind of muscular complication in which the head of the affected people rotates to the chin\'s opposite side.\n This type of complication can have various causes.\n the causes of which are mentioned in the sections.\n and it is the most common type of complication in congenital infants.\n</string>
    <string name="elat_gardane_kaj">Congenital factors include 1- Injury to the neck during childbirth.\n 2- The possibility of improper placement of the fetal neck in the uterus.\n Acquired factors include 1- Traumas to the neck that cause bleeding in the sternum-lumbar-mammary muscle.\n which becomes the scar tissue of the scar over time.\n The presence of this tissue causes the muscle to shorten.\n resulting in torticollis.\n 2- Unilateral contraction of the sternum-torus-mammary muscle.\n 3- Improper maintenance of the head for a long time such as study.\n 4- Drugs.\n 5- Alcohol.\n 6- Cervical disc diseases.\n 7- Tumors</string>
    <string name="test_gardane_kaj">1- Using a checkered plane and a vertical line.\n 2- Asymmetry of the distance between the corners and the surface of the shoulders.\n 2- Placement of the head on one side and rotation of the face and asymmetry of the jaw and face.\n 4- Connecting the shock appendages to each other and measuring the deviation of the spine.\n 5- Using radiography images</string>

    <string name="areze_paye_god">A supinated foot is an abnormality in which the foot\'s longitudinal arch has an abnormal increase and is often accompanied by a claw toe.\n </string>
    <string name="elat_paye_god">This complication is etiologically divided into congenital acquired and idiopathic types (with unknown cause).\n In the acquired type.\n this complication can be caused by one of the following reasons: 1- Shortness of the soft tissue of the sole of the foot.\n 2- Weakness of the smoky muscles and interosseous muscles.\n 3- Weakness of the extensor muscle of the toes with the anterior tibia 4- Excessive activity of muscles that are connected in the sole of the foot.\n including long thin reeds.\n 5- Short Achilles tendon.\n 6- Paralysis of the triceps muscles.\n 7- Excessive activity of the soleus muscles and flexor muscles of the toes.\n 8- Excessive activity of toe opener muscle.\n </string>
    <string name="test_paye_god">1- Sitting position of the knees.\n bend the heels on the ground.\n rotate the foot outwards.\n and try to open and move the toes apart.\n 2- Try to stretch the sole of the foot with your hands and a towel that has passed under the sole of the foot.\n 3- In a sitting position.\n like the previous exercise.\n using your hands or a towel.\n try to open your toes\' end and middle straps.\n 4- In the standing position.\n open the claws from each other in the form of a fan.\n 5- In a sitting position.\n with the help of your hands.\n press the first strap of your toes down.\n and the other straps up.\n 6- In the sitting position.\n try to bring the heel to the ground and stretch the sole of the foot in the starting position of the sprinters.\n 7- In the standing position.\n try to lift the toes and bring the back of the foot closer to the leg.\n  </string>

    <string name="areze_paye_saf">The forces on foot are transmitted to the ground from three points of the heel below the head of the first sole of the foot and below the head of the fifth sole of the foot.\n On the other hand.\n three arches on each sole; there is an inner longitudinal.\n outer longitudinal.\n and transverse arc.\n The reduction or disappearance of the inner longitudinal arch of the sole of the foot is called a flat foot.\n   </string>
    <string name="elat_paye_saf">1- People who stand for a long time.\n hairdressers.\n weightlifters who train for a long time.\n 2- Wearing non-standard shoes.\n 3- To people who are hospitalized for a long time.\n A: Due to muscle and ligament weakness.\n B: These people are prone to osteoporosis.\n which causes osteoporosis in the early stages lea to softens and then leads to flat foot.\n 4- In athletes who have leg pain.\n bruises on the back of the leg muscles to reduce foot pain.\n rotated outward.\n and in case of excessive repetition causes flat foot.\n 5- Obesity.\n 6- Ligament laxity.\n 7- Flat foot has a muscular cause.\n general inefficiency of posterior and anterior tibialis muscle and long.\n long flexors of toe tips thumb.\n as well as soleus muscles.\n is evident in the occurrence of this complication.\n 8- Sleeping with the baby on his stomach causes him to be able to turn inwards.\n and the base rotators are shortened outside.\n 9- Sitting the child in a W position makes the sole of the child flat.\n 10- Reducing the angle of the thigh\'s head and neck causes the knee to cross.\n and then the sole of the foot.\n 11- Shortening of outer ligaments such as thin reed-heel and heel-heel 12- Shortening of lateral thinning muscles and shortening of Achilles tendon.\n 13- Hereditary factors.\n  </string>
    <string name="test_paye_saf">Using plaster.\n talcum powder.\n or water and examining the role of footprints on the floor or carpet.\n 2- By examining the skin color of the soles of the feet.\n the points that are in contact with the ground are red.\n and their skin is thicker.\n and the areas that are far from the ground.\n their skin is whiter and more sensitive.\n 3- Examination of the Achilles tendon in people with a flat foot.\n the Achilles tendon deviates outwards.\n 4- Using a pedoscope in examining the sole of the foot with a pedoscope.\n the places that bear the weight become whiter.\n and the places that are far from the ground or that do not bear the weight become darker or redder.\n 5- If we draw a line from under the inner ankle to the end of the first sole of the foot.\n in this case.\n if the navicular bone is below this line.\n it indicates the flatness of the sole of the foot.\n Note: Attach a linear heel bone to the head of the third sole of the foot.\n This line is the boundary between the inner longitudinal arch and the outer longitudinal arc.\n The closer we get to the first toe and the greater the contact of the sole of the foot with the ground from the borderline to these points.\n the more flat the foot is.\n 6- Checking the height of the foot\'s internal longitudinal arch.\n normally less than two toes can be trampled underfoot.\n  </string>

    <string name="areze_lagan">The asymmetric pelvis is a complication in which the deformity of the iliac crest of the two sides is not aligned with each other.\n In the horizontal position.\n it appears that when the pelvic support and stabilizing factors are disturbed on one side.\n it causes the pelvis to rotate laterally.\n </string>
    <string name="elat_lagan">1- Shortness of one leg\'s extensor muscles causes the pelvis to fall on the same side.\n 2- Shortness of the muscles approaching one leg causes the pelvis to rise in the same direction.\n 3- Shortness of one leg; if the length of one leg is shorter (whether apparent or actual short) than the other leg.\n the pelvis will sag on that side.\n 4 - Scoliosis and uneven shoulder complication can also lead to this complication.\n  </string>
    <string name="test_lagan">The people stand normally.\n and the therapist identifies the iliac crest on both sides of the pelvis.\n then connects them with a ruler.\n If the iliac crest is not in a horizontal line.\n it indicates the pelvis is inclined.\n Radiographic photography: Another test to diagnose the Thomas test is to perform this simple test: • Lie on a bed with your legs hanging from your knees at the edge of the bed.\n •Then stretch one leg toward your chest and bend your knee.\n Then repeat for the other leg.\n • If the pelvis is not level.\n the back of the foot hanging from the edge of the bed will rise from the bed.\n If the people are forced to pull or rotate the leg that hangs from the edge of the bed to prevent it from rising.\n it indicates that the pelvis is asymmetric.\n </string>

    <string name="areze_paye_x">There is no distance between the knees and the ankles under normal circumstances when the person lies on their back and pairs their legs.\n In some people.\n when lying down.\n when the legs are paired.\n their ankles are separated.\n in which case the person has a crossed leg or X-knee.\n or in the scientific term genu valgum.\n </string>
    <string name="elat_paye_x">1- Baby walking early.\n 2- Excessive obesity.\n 3- Bad sitting habits.\n 4- Softness of bones.\n 5- Fractures that are badly welded.\n 6- Rupture of inner lateral ligaments.\n 7- The sometimes flat foot is the cause of genu valgum.\n </string>
    <string name="test_paye_x">By measuring the tibial angle on X-ray images of the foot.\n the genu valgum can be divided into four parts: 1.\n Garde 1.\n where the distance between the two ankles is less than an inch.\n 2- Grade 2.\n where the distance between the two ankles is between one and two inches.\n 3- Grade 3.\n where the distance between the two ankles is between two to three inches.\n 4- Grade 4.\n where the distance between the two ankles is more than three inches</string>

    <string name="areze_paye_parantezi">In this deformity.\n the knees move away from each other.\n and the inner ankles get closer together.\n and the legs become braced.\n which is why it is called a genu varum.\n All babies have a genu varum at birth and childhood that gradually changes shape from a brace to a cross as the legs grow.\n Note: To diagnose foot abnormalities.\n we need to know the knee\'s normal position at different ages: A- The newborn has a medium genu varum.\n B.\n A six-month-old baby has a very small amount of genu varum.\n C- The child has a flat foot for a year.\n D.\n A one-year-old and sixmonth-old child has a physiologically (normal) genu valgum.\n The two-year-old and six-monthold baby have a protective rotation of the toes inward.\n E- A four- to a six-year-old child has a flat foot.\n</string>
    <string name="elat_paye_parantezi">Obesity or overweight.\n 2- Baby walking early.\n 3- Fractures of the joint surfaces or fractures of the bones at the top or bottom of the joint.\n 4- Excessive use of diapers.\n5- Shortness of the membranous muscles and the inner hemisphere of the leg.\n 6- Muscular weakness of the biceps (Outside of the foot).\n 7- Rupture of the outer lateral ligament of the knee.\n 8- Hereditary background.\n 9- Bone softness (rickets) </string>
    <string name="test_paye_parantezi">To diagnose brace deformities of genu varum while the people are lying on his back and his patella is facing forward.\n we measure the distance between the knee\'s two inner condyles with a caliper.\n If the distance is less than two and a half centimeters.\n it is normal.\n and if it is more than that.\n it is genu varum.\n  </string>

    <string name="areze_poshte_god">Excessive lumbar enlargement is called lordosis.\n In this deformity.\n the amount of lumbar spine becomes too normal and the outer lumbar angle.\n which is about 30 degrees in healthy people.\n The anterior rotation of the pelvis also increases.\n and the hip joints become bent.\n The buttocks protrude to the back.\n and the knees may be bent or pressed back.\n In a low back deformity.\n the abdomen hangs forward.\n and the shoulders may be pulled back.\n turning around and causing kyphosis.\n The entire weight is pulled backward toward the heels.\n </string>
    <string name="elat_poshte_god">1- Weakness of abdominal muscles.\n  2- Shortness of Suez\'s iliac and right thigh muscles.\n 2- Weakness of hamstring muscles.\n 4- Compensatory increase of dorsal kyphosis and lumbar lordosis.\n as a result.\n 5- Use of high heels.\n 6- Frequent deliveries.\n 7- Congenital hip dislocation bilaterally.\n 8.\n Move the vertebrae forward.\n </string>
    <string name="test_poshte_god">1- Using the lumbar vertebrae side and measuring the outer lumbar angle.\n we can comment on the lumbar hump.\n If the angle is more than 30 degrees.\n we can say that the lumbar hump has increased.\n 2- Using a vertical line and a checkerboard (The people are placed in the vertical line to the side).\n If most of the lumbar region is in front of the lateral line compared to the vertical line.\n it can be said that the lumbar region has increased.\n 3- Matthias test: In this test.\n the people are asked to stand with his hands forward for 30 seconds and place them along the ground and keep his body upright and straight.\n If during this time their body is deformed and their upper torso is tilted back.\n and the pelvis of the pelvis deviates forward.\n these complications should indicate the weakness of the muscles that support the body\'s spine.\n 4- Thomas test: The Thomas test is used to assess the Shortness of the thigh\'s flexor muscles.\n including the iliac crest and the right thigh.\n The people lie on his back.\n bends one leg at the knee and thigh.\n and approaches the chest.\n If the other leg is lifted from the hip joint.\n it indicates Shortness in the thigh\'s flexor muscles.\n The higher the angle of the thigh.\n the shorter the muscle.\n </string>

    <string name="areze_poshte_kaj">Scoliosis is a deviation of the vertebral column so that the vertebrae\'s shock appendages rotate towards concavity.\n and the body of the vertebrae rotates towards convexity.\n Unlike the normal conditions of kyphosis or lordosis.\n which are naturally present in all people.\n this condition is always abnormal.\n The word Scoliosis is derived from the Greek word meaning crooked and is one of the most common deformities of the spine.\n The term was first used by cows to mean abnormal curvature of the spine.\n It is generally agreed that lateral curvature of the spine is known as Scoliosis when the curvature is more than ten degrees.\n This attitude puts a large number of people in the normal group with a deviation of fewer than ten degrees.\n Scoliosis is a disorder that develops in childhood and adolescence and persists into old age.\n  </string>
    <string name="elat_poshte_kaj">1- Shortening of the thigh muscles in one leg; this shortening causes the pelvis to fall on the muscles\' shortened side.\n followed by Scoliosis in the spine.\n Scoliosis begins in the outer lumbar region.\n 2.\n Shortening of the muscles near the thigh in one leg.\n This shortening causes the pelvic floor to rise towards the shortened muscles.\n followed by Scoliosis in the spine Scoliosis starts from the lumbar-outer region.\n 3.\n Shortness of one leg Shortness of the leg causes the pelvis to fall on the side of the short leg.\n followed by Scoliosis.\n Scoliosis begins in the lumbar-outer region.\n 4- Adopting inappropriate postures such as carrying objects with one hand.\n which leads to Scoliosis.\n 5- Habit of sitting on one side.\n 6- Sciatica; A person may have a disc herniation.\n and the muscles on one side are weakened.\n which can lead to Scoliosis.\n </string>
    <string name="test_poshte_kaj">1- You should pay attention to the position of the pelvis while sitting.\n Both hips should be level.\n a people with a smaller pelvis on one side does not have both hips on the same level.\n 2- In the standing position.\n the iliac crest should be in a line on both sides of the pelvis.\n If the pelvis is one side higher.\n it indicates Scoliosis.\n 3- The upper posterior iliac spines should be level.\n 4- When standing.\n if we connect the lower angles in the scapula.\n it should be in a line.\n In people with Scoliosis.\n these angles are not in a line.\n </string>

    <string name="areze_sar_be_jelo">In the forward head.\n the head\'s center of gravity is in front of the vertical line.\n It is said that in this abnormality.\n the cervical arch increases.\n and a lot of pressure is put on the temporomandibular joints and the joints of the neck and the muscles behind the neck.\n Two types of this type of complication can be named.\n 1- Head forward with increased cervical lordosis.\n This type of head forward with increased cervical lordosis with the skull\'s posterior rotation causes the muscles behind the neck to shorten and the muscles in the front of the neck to stretch.\n 2- The head is forward with the neck lordosis smooth and without posterior rotation of the skull</string>
    <string name="elat_sar_be_jelo">One of the causes of this complication is poor eyesight.\n which is pulled forward to see better.\n When resting.\n the use of long pillows keeps the head in inappropriate positions.\n such as when using a mobile phone or while reading.\n etc.\n </string>
    <string name="test_sar_be_jelo">1- Using a checkered plane and a vertical line in which the asymmetry of the two points of the eardrum distance and the appendix is not in the same direction.\n 2- The head protrudes.\n and the chin rises.\n 3- The use of radiograph and spine examination.\n 4- On the neck joints in the back area.\n 5- Premature fatigue in the muscles of the back neck area.\n 6- Stiffness and contraction of the back muscles of the neck.\n 7- Bad pairing of teeth 8- Neck pain in the back and temporal.\n occipital region.\n</string>

    <string name="areze_shane">The abnormality of the shoulders and the lowness of one shoulder relative to the other shoulder are called uneven or asymmetrical shoulders or sagging shoulders.\n or in scientific terms.\n uneven shoulder.\n This abnormality is seen unilaterally or bilaterally.\n</string>
    <string name="elat_shane">1- Adopting the wrong position when sitting.\n standing.\n sleeping.\n walking.\n sports activities such as table tennis.\n and throwing exercises.\n 2- Carrying bags and books with one hand.\n 3- Weakness of the trapezius muscle\'s scapular muscles and upper fibers on one side.\n 4- Imbalance of the muscles that support the shoulder girdle.\n 5- Weakness of the muscles around the shoulder.\n 6- Dislocation of the sternoclavicular joint.\n </string>
    <string name="test_shane">1- Inequality of the lower angle of the shoulders indirect observation.\n 2- In standing position and free and released hands.\n both hands\' toe tips are not in line.\n 3- Inequality of the lower angle of the shoulder.\n 4- Inequality of the last two appendages  of the clavicle.\n 5- Inequality of the angle of the neck to the shoulder 6- Reduction of the range of motion of the hand.\n </string>

    <string name="areze_shast">In hallux valgus.\n the thumb approaches the second toe.\n and the first thumb bends more than ten degrees outward relative to the first sole of the foot.\n In the advanced stages of this complication.\n the thumb is placed on the second toe or below it.\n</string>
    <string name="elat_shast">In most cases.\n this complication is inherited and congenital.\n </string>
    <string name="test_shast">By observing the thumb.\n we can realize the existence of this complication.\n and it is in this way that the thumb is close to the second toe.\n and sometimes it is placed on the second toe or below it.\n  </string>

    <string name="areze_chakoshi">The hammer toe is a contraction or bending of the toe at the site of its first joint.\n called the proximal interphalangeal joint.\n This bending causes the toe to have the appearance of the letter V upside down when viewed from the side.\n This problem can affect any of the toes.\n but it is most common on the second to fifth toes or smaller toes.\n The problem of hammertoe is more common among women.\n and men are less likely than women to have this problem.\n In hammer toe complication.\n the joint between the first and second joints of the toes is inflection.\n and the joint between the second and third joints of the toes.\n as well as the sole-toe joint.\n is in hyperextension.\n i.\ne.\n.\n • MTP joint hyperextension.\n • PIP joint flexion - hyperextension The DIP joint has two types of hammertoes: 1- Flexible and movable.\n • In the movable hammer toe.\n the affected joint or joints are not completely fixed and are partially flattened by the force of the hand with another outer force.\n • Disruption of joint range of motion in this type is due to the Shortness and weakness of soft tissue.\n • Can be modified with corrective movement.\n 2- Rigid • In this type of complication.\n the affected joint or joints have lost their range of motion.\n and a joint stiffness has developed that causes pain and limited mobility.\n In this case.\n even with the hand force\'s help.\n the joint can not be returned to its original natural state.\n They can usually not be repaired with non-surgical methods because the hard tissue is also affected.\n</string>
    <string name="elat_chakoshi"> Osteoarthritis.\n 2- Heredity.\n 3- Bruising.\n 4- Increased arch of the foot.\n 5- Neuromuscular diseases Shortness of flexor muscles of toes.\n 6- Abnormal length of the second toe.\n 7- Dislocation and partial dislocation of toe joints.\n 8- Weakness of extensor muscles of toes and muscles Soles of the feet.\n 9- Imbalance between the strength of the muscles of flexion and extension of the toes.\n 10- Use of high-heeled shoes with narrow and tight toes as well as tight socks.\n </string>
    <string name="test_chakoshi">1- Formation of corns.\n 2- Deformation of nails.\n 3- Pain in the joints of the toes.\n 4- Calluses on the middle joint of the toes.\n 5- Shortness of the flexor muscle of the long toes.\n 6- Redness and swelling at the point of contraction of the toe joint.\n 7- Pain in the spherical area of the sole of the foot at the base of the toes.\n 8- Pain of the tips of the bent toes when the shoe applies pressure.\n 9.\n Bending (flexion) of the middle toe joint and opening (extension) of the sole of the foot- toe and the joint between the second and third joints  </string>

    <string name="areze_changali">The claw toe: the toe joint is in hyper-extension mode.\n and the first and second toe joints are in inflection mode.\n This abnormality is usually accompanied by a complication of the sole of the foot and involves more than four outer toes.\n The difference between a hammertoe and a claw toe: The only structural difference between these two complications is that in the second hammertoe.\n the toe joint (DIP) is in hyper-extension mode.\n but in the claw toe.\n this joint (DIP) is in flexion mode.\n  </string>
    <string name="elat_changali">1- Weakness of the soleus and extensor muscles of the toes.\n 2- Shortness of the flexor muscles of the toes.\n 2- Soles of the supinated foot.\n 4- Use of high heels with narrow and tight toes.\n 5- Use of tight socks.\n 6- Inheritance </string>
    <string name="test_changali">1- The toes are bent upwards from the joints under the toe.\n 2. The toes are bent from the middle joints to the sole of the shoe and down.\n 3- Sometimes the toes in the upper joints are bent downwards and twist underfoot 4.\n There is a possibility of corns on the toes or under the toes.\n</string>

    <string name="shast_one">In a sitting situation.\n take the thumb and pull it inward</string>
    <string name="shast_two">In a standing situation.\n place the thumb\'s back on the ground and bend it firmly at a maximum range of motion</string>
    <string name="shast_three">Wrap a sturdy plastic band around your toes and separate your toes</string>
    <string name="shast_four">In a standing situation.\n while standing.\n walk with your thumbs clenched together.\n </string>
    <string name="shast_five">Close your thumb using a suitable splint</string>
    <string name="connect_us">connect us</string>
    <string name="choose_language">language</string>
    <string name="exit">exit</string>
    <string name="height">height(cm)</string>
    <string name="weight">weight(kg)</string>
    <string name="calculate">  calculate  </string>
    <string name="sex">sex:</string>
    <string name="male">male</string>
    <string name="female">female</string>
    <string name="weight_kg">weight(kg)</string>
    <string name="height_m">height(cm)</string>
    <string name="age">age(year)</string>
    <string name="bmi_btn">  BMI  </string>
    <string name="calculate_btn">  calculate...  </string>
    <string name="bmr_btn">  BMR  </string>
    <string name="corrective_exercises">  corrective exercises  </string>
    <string name="more">  more...  </string>
    <string name="about_btn">  about  </string>
    <string name="correct_value">Enter the values correctly!</string>
    <string name="calories_one">At rest.\n your body needs </string>
    <string name="calories_two"> kilo calories per day</string>
    <string name="enter_values">Enter the values!</string>
    <string name="bmi_resault">your BMI result is </string>
    <string name="name">Corrective exercises</string>
    <string name="damghan_univercity">Sports Science. Damghan University</string>
    <string name="Treatment">Treatment of muscle pain</string>
    <string name="fat">Are you thin or fat?</string>
    <string name="body">Beautiful Body</string>
    <string name="reason">reason</string>
    <string name="exercise">exercise</string>
    <string name="test">test</string>
    <string name="title_changali">The exercises for the claw toe and hammer toe are the same</string>
    <string name="back">don\'t forget rating us!\nPress back again to exit!</string>
    <string name="check_connction">you need internet connection here!</string>
    <string name="bidemajnoongroup">BideMajnoon Group</string>


</resources>


